A Guide to the Virginia Dept. of Military Affairs, Adjutant General Interwar unit files, 1918-1941
Library of Virginia
- Presidential visit to Roanoke (Va.) [File 560], 1934 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Materials pertaining to the military code [File 561], 1924-1930 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Virginia Military Institute Reports [File 562], 1919-1929 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Virginia Military Institute Reports [File 562], 1930-1937 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Claims against the federal government for WWI mobilization [File 563], 1916-1922 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Naming of Derigable ZR3 as "the Virginia" [File 564] (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Medical costs [File 565], 1932-1936 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- State Military Reservation Material [File 566], 1919-1921 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- State Military Reservation Material [File 566], 1922-1923 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- State Military Reservation Material [File 567], 1924 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- State Military Reservation Material [File 567], 1925-1928 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- State Military Reservation Material [File 568], 1929-1930 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- State Military Reservation Material [File 568], 1931-1933 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- State Military Reservation Material [File 569], 1934-1935 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- State Military Reservation Publicity [File 570], 1931-1933 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Misc. training plans [File 571], 1926-1927 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Material on State Rifle Team [File 572], 1931-1932 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 573], 1919-1924 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 574], 1925 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 575], 1926-1928 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 576], 1930 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 576], 1931 January (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 576], 1931 February-April (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 577], 1932 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 578], 1933 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 579], 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 580], 1936 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Aid to Civil Authority [File 581], 1937 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Minutes of the Military Board [File 582], 1919-1922 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- History and Heraldy, 1st Infantry (176th, 183rd) [File 583], 1920-1936 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- History and Heraldy, 116th Infantry (2nd) [File 584] (Box 25, Folder 10)
- History and Heraldy, 111th Field Artillery [File 585], 1923-1930 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- History and Heraldy, 246th Coast Artillery [File 586], 1923-1936 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- History and Heraldy, 104th Medical Regiment [File 587], 1923-1927 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- History and Heraldy, 29th Tank Company [File 588], 1925-1928 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Imcomplete roster of previous Adjutant Generals [File 589], 1920-1921 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- List of summer camps since 1903, [File 590] (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Report of activities under Governor Pollard [File 591], 1933 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Materials on the disposition of colors (flags) [File 592], 1919-1936 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Allocations of positions in the 29th Division [File 593], 1923-1924 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Inquiries from Towns, A-C [File 594], 1919-1921 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Inquiries from Towns, C-F, [File 594], 1919-1921 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Inquiries from Towns, F-L [File 594], 1919-1921 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Inquiries from Towns, L-M [File 594], 1919-1921 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Inquiries from Towns, N-P [File 595], 1919-1921 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Inquiries from Towns, P-W [File 595] (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Inquiries from Towns, Misc. [File 596], 1923-1939 (Box 27, Folder 1-7)
- Organization, General [File 597], 1919-1935 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- 91st (88th) Infantry Brigade (Berryville) [File 598], 1921-1922 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- 54th Field Artillery Brigade (Norfolk, Richmond) [File 599], 1925-1934 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- 104th Medical Regiment, General [File 600], 1919-1937 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- 104th Medical Regiment, Company D (Norfolk) [File 601], 1919-1936 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- 104th Medical Regiment, Company G (Danville) [File 602], 1921-1936 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- 104th Quartermaster Regiment, General [File 603], 1936-1937 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- 29th Signal Company (Norfolk) [File 604], 1920-1932 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- 29th Tank Company (Danville) [File 605], 1921-1930 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- 1st Infantry, General (also 176th, 183rd) [File 606], 1921-1930 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Headquarters Company (Richmond) [File 607], 1920-1929 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Antitank Company (Norfolk) [File 608], 1929 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Service Company (Richmond) [File 609], 1919-1934 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Band (Petersburg) [File 610], 1920-1934 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Medical Detachment (Petersburg) [File 611], 1920-1936 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, 3rd Battalion, Headquarters Company (Onancock) [File 612], 1920-1929 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, 1st Battalion (Richmond Light Infantry Blues) [File 613], 1919-1936 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Company E (Hopewell) [File 614], 1921-1929 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Company F (Blackstone) [File 615], 1919-1929 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Company G (Petersburg) [File 616], 1919-1929 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Company H (Richmond) [File 617], 1919-1929 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Company I (Alexandria) [File 618], 1919-1929 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Company I (Norfolk) [File 619], 1919-1927 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Company K (Suffolk) [File 620], 1919-1924 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Company K (Norfolk) [File 621], 1923-1929 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Company L and M (Newport News) [File 622], 1919-1929 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- 1st Infantry Regiment, Company M (Norfolk) [File 623], 1924-1929 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- 2nd Infantry Regiment (116th), General [File 624], 1921-1937 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Headquarters Company (Roanoke) [File 625], 1925-1926 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Headquarters Company (Surry) [File 626], 1921-1925 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Antitank Company (Roanoke) [File 627] (Box 29, Folder 12)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Howitzer Company (Chatham) [File 628], 1920-1923 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Service Company (Roanoke) [File 629], 1919-1936 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Band (Roanoke) [File 630], 1921-1922 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Medical Dept. (Wytheville and Staunton) [File 631], 1924-1931 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company A (Bedford) [File 632], 1920-1921 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company B (Lynchburg) [File 633], 1919-1921 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company C (Harrisonburg) [File 634], 1926 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company C (Abingdon) [File 635], 1920-1926 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company D (Roanoke) [File 636], 1920-1927 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company E (Charles City) [File 637], 1919-1921 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company F (South Boston) [File 638], 1919-1936 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company G (Farmville) [File 639], 1920-1921 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company H (Martinsville) [File 640], 1920-1936 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company I (Winchester) [File 641], 1919-1921 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company K (Charlottesville) [File 642], 1919-1922 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company L (Staunton) [File 643], 1919-1921 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- 116th Infantry Regiment, Company M (Emporia) [File 644] (Box 30, Folder 15)
- 111th Field Artillery, General [File 645], 1921-1935 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- 111th Field Artillery, Battery A (Richmond) [File 646], 1919-1922 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- 111th Field Artillery, Battery B (Norfolk) [File 647], 1919-1928 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- 111th Field Artillery, Battery C (Portsmouth) [File 648], 1919-1929 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- 111th Field Artillery, Battery D (Hampton) [File 649], 1927 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- 111th Field Artillery, Battery E (Richmond) [File 650], 1922 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- 111th Field Artillery, Battery F (Fredericksburg) [File 651], 1922-1928 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- 111th Field Artillery, Service Battery (Newport News) [File 652], 1922-1931 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- 111th Field Artillery, Band (Norfolk) [File 653], 1922-1930 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- 111th Field Artillery, Medical Detachment (Norfolk) [File 654], 1926-1937 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- 246th Coast Artillery, General [File 655], 1920-1934 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Band (Lynchburg and Danville) [File 656], 1922-1929 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Medical Detachment (Roanoke) [File 657], 1922 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Battery A (Richmond) [File 658], 1921 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Battery B (Danville) [File 659], 1919-1927 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Battery B (Gordonsville) [File 660], 1921-1924 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Battery C (Clifton Forge) [File 661], 1920-1922 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Battery D (Covington and Buchanan) [File 662], 1921-1924 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Battery E (Lynchburg) [File 663], 1919-1921 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Battery F (Blacksburg) [File 664], 1922-1923 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Battery H (Christiansburg) [File 665], 1921-1928 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Battery H (Vinton) [File 666], 1928 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- 246th Coast Artillery, Battery I (Roanoke) [File 667], 1921-1922 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- 415th Coast Artillery (Chincotague) [File 668], 1922-1923 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Officer Service Records, A [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Officer Service Records, B [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Officer Service Records, C [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Officer Service Records, D [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Officer Service Records, E [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Officer Service Records, F [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Officer Service Records, G [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Officer Service Records, H [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Officer Service Records, I-J [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Officer Service Records, K [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Officer Service Records, L [File 216], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Officer Service Records, M [File 217], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Officer Service Records, N [File 217], 1918 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Officer Service Records, P [File 217], 1918 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Officer Service Records, R [File 217], 1918 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Officer Service Records, S [File 217], 1918 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Officer Service Records, T [File 217], 1918 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Officer Service Records, V [File 217], 1918 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Officer Service Records, W [File 217], 1918 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Officer Service Records, Y [File 217], 1918 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Oversize folder, 1918-1941 (Folder 1)